(dramatic orchestral music plays)
When our voices rise from quiet ground.
Our songs are scribbled on life's pages
unbound.
Every word a seed in the heart it finds.
We are
ready to chant the great hymns of time.
We will sing with Magdalene on every
scroll the
stars design. On every sacred
scribbled line. Let the melody
carve a light in every echo
lost in time. Forever we will
sing with Magdalene.
(dramatic orchestral music plays) As time
fades our
scribbled pages.
And our hearts lie in forgotten
stages.
Let the silence still remember our song.
A melody that forever belongs. Not
today, not tomorrow, but forever. We will
sing with Magdalene on every scroll the
stars
design. On every sacred scribbled
line. Let the melody carve a
light in every echo lost in time.
Forever we will sing with Magdalene.
(dramatic orchestral music plays)
We will sing with Magdalene on every
scroll the stars design. On every
sacred scribbled line. Let the
melody carve a light in every
echo lost in time. Forever we will sing
with Magdalene. We will sing with
Magdalene. We will sing with
Magdalene on every scroll the stars
design. On every sacred scribbled
line. Magdalene.
(dramatic orchestral music plays) And when
time fades our scribbled
pages.
And our hearts lie in forgotten
stages.
Let the silence still remember our song.
A melody that forever belongs. Not
today, not tomorrow, but forever.
(music fades out)